Jiaojiao,
what are you doing this time?
Martial arts tournament for marriage.
You've been telling people I love street fights.
I might as well set up a ring
and find a strong guy.
If you're so eager to get married,
you'll surely find a good husband.
It seems you're even more anxious than me.
Watch and see.
Hmph!
[Steamed buns!]
[Freshly made steamed buns!]
That's strange.
Not a single soul around.
Su's Escort Agency.
The escort lives with the escort.
Oh.
Forget it, Jiaojiao.
No one will come.
Sir,
if you want to stay in the inn,
you have to wait until tomorrow morning.
If you want to drink,
you have to wait until noon.
Who said we were here to stay at an inn?
My young master is here to attend the Nebula Assembly.
Nebula Assembly?
Please leave your previous works and names.
If they are approved by my young lady,
you will be qualified to participate in the Nebula Assembly.
Come to Huayue Tower on the 15th
for the preliminary contest.
We are from other places.
If we come but can't participate,
wouldn't it be a wasted trip?
Yunjing residents.
If you're talented,
it won't be a wasted trip.
I thought
the Nebula Assembly was for talented people from all over the world.
I didn't expect it to be...
Okay.
Thank you.
Please support me at the Nebula Assembly.
Impossible.
I've already changed it.
Please.
You took five hits.
You win.
Really?
When do I start?
Start working?
Aren't you here for the marriage selection?
Aren't you hiring for odd jobs?
Then why are you fighting me?
You started it!
Gong Xi, Fa Cai,
let's go.
Let's get to work now.
I'll go home and pack up.
He's good at martial arts.
We can hire him
can be considered.
Although I don't know Kungfu,
but
I'll be the head of the Escort Agency.
And I'll be in charge of the money.
Ah.
Gong Xi
Write it outside.
Make a living, support the wife and educate the children.
Uncle
Your son should do it himself.
I can do it myself.
I'm in good health.
I just want to know
how much money you can give me.
My friend,
if you marry into our Su family,
you can
call me grandfather.
I'm in good health.
Ha ha ha.
Hahaha.
Please teach me.
The legendary one-leg stand.
Su Yuejiao,
enough is enough.
No one would set rules like yours.
Are my rules too much?
This is a marriage selection,
not recruiting escort.
Oh,
listen to me,
You'd better find a man to marry.
Why do you have to recruit a son-in-law?
Why do you have to ask?
Whether I get married or not, I won't leave the Escort Agency.
Do you want to take over the Agency?
Dad
Ah.
You're so grown up but still don't understand.
You don't know to save my dad's heart.
You should do the same.
You...
Don't think you can be rude because you're good at martial arts.
I'm your senior after all.
You are always idling away your time.
You either run up bills at the inn or lose the escort.
You were even taken to the police station.
Senior?
I won't let you ruin the Escort Agency anymore.
Su Yuejiao
You're not in charge of the escort agency now.
Leave me alone.
By the way,
pay the bill of Huayue Tower for me.
Alas.
Jiaojiao.
Brother, can you stand this?
I can't stand it anymore,
but I have to.
He is spoiled by Grandma and Mother.
No.
You spoiled him.
Well.
Don't be angry.
It's more important to recruit a son-in-law.
Tang Xin always has a lot of ideas.
Why don't you ask her for advice?
You have been sisters for many years.
Except me,
only she and Grandpa won't hurt you.
Why don't you listen to her?
Da Qi is right.
You should have listened to me.
Put the notice here.
The Nebula Assembly is coming.
There will be many young talents.
I'll help you find a good husband.
Okay.
Are you sure?
How many people
in your Huayue Tower are willing to...
Open your mind.
This is Yunjing.
There is nothing impossible
but unimaginable.
Maybe a man will fall from the sky.
Don't laugh at me.
The Su family is recruiting a son-in-law again.
Why don't you go and sign up?
I'm the only son in my family.
How can I marry into a woman's family?
It sounds like you can marry into a woman's family,
and you dare to marry her.
Who dares to marry her?
Why not?
The girl of the Su family
grew up fighting in the streets.
She is fierce and hot-tempered.
If you marry her, you'll be beaten every day.
Yeah.
Have you ever met her?
You just talk nonsense.
Think about it.
A woman as an escort.
and fights all day.
It's not decent at all.
Yeah.
Is there a rule that women can't be escorts?
A wife should help her husband and educate the children.
She can't do that.
You can do that?
How?
Hey, how dare you talk like that?
Who are you?
I...
I am
Su Yuejiao.
Sir, be careful.
But
will posting notices here affect the escort agency's reputation?
When my dad escorted goods with your mom,
he always mentioned
what is the most important thing for an escort agency.
The escort lives with the escort.
As long as the escort is well delivered,
and the price is reasonable,
no one cares how you recruit a son-in-law.
Well, you know,
I want to be the head of the family,
not because I want to compete with my uncle,
nor because of the rules set by my grandmother.
I just want to protect the escort agency
my mother has guarded for a lifetime.
If I had a sister who could run the family,
I just wanted to be a small escort.
I understand.
My mother is a musician.
I also like music theory.
So I became a musician.
It's a pity that your three brothers are not hard-working.
You have to take the responsibility.
But have you thought it over?
Are you willing to marry someone for the escort agency?
What can I do?
I can only become the Seal Keeper after getting married.
No one told me about this rule before.
When I'm almost an adult,
Su Lishi suddenly jumped out and interfered.
But for me,
it doesn't matter who I marry.
I just want to stay in the Escort Agency.
It's good not to suffer from love.
Unlike me,
I like a block of wood.
I'll be killed by anger or suffocation.
Who dares to make you angry?
I'll beat him up.
Jiaojiao
You are the best.
I have another idea.
What idea?
Matchmaker Pavilion
Wow.
Miss, what brings you here?
I haven't seen that man before.
He's an outsider
for the Star Conference.
Show me his paper.
Okay.
He's got some talent,
but his writing's all form, no soul.
Put him at the bottom of the list.
Got it.
Is the newly opened Matchmaker Pavilion
that good?
Our Shopkeeper Li
was widowed for years.
But recently,
the Matchmaker Pavilion found him a wife.
They got married in a month.
Mr. Li got married?
Then why do I need to post the notice?
Tell me how to get to the Matchmaker Pavilion.
Young Master,
we risked
punishment from the master to come here.
This Nebula Assembly is so unfair.
How can we come out
in half a month?
As long as we have a reason.
Wake up, Young Master.
You neither take the exam nor study in the academy.
This time,
the master will never let you out.
There is only one way to make him agree.
Su Yuejiao's advertisement
is even posted in the Huayue Tower.
A hefty reward for a son-in-law.
Su's Escort Agency is good.
Why don't you have a try?
There are indeed a lot of people.
I don't know if it will work this time.
I have to leave a successor for my family.
But I can't be a live-in son-in-law.
The rice is too soft for me.
It's quite suitable for you.
It's suitable for you.
Chief Escort Su, what a coincidence.
The food is soft.
I think you've lost your teeth.
I think you've lost your legs.
You have such a bad temper.
Do you still want to be the head of the family?
I really can't deal with you.
I'd better not go to the Matchmaker Pavilion.
It may be unreliable.
Miss,
I heard you're looking for a son-in-law.
May I apply for the position?